Break through myself!
（Break through myself!）
Break through myself!!
（Break through myself!!）
Break through myself!!!
（Break through myself!!!）
Make a stand against
Beat your heart
（GO!）
（Victor…）
さあ目|<めを覚|<さませ
降|<ふり注|<そ#|そぐ過|<か去|<こさえも振|<ふり払|<は#|らって
'Cause I'll never yield
指|<さし示|<し#|めす道|<み#|ちの向|<むこうへ
叫|<さ#|けび声|<ご#|え上|<あげて
痛|<い#|たみさえも
立|<たち止|<どまる理|<り由|<ゆ#|うにはならない
からただ進|<す#|すめよ
Don't be afraid to die
終|<おわらせない掴|<つ#|かみ取|<とるまでは
Just getting over the end
ここにしかない光|<ひ#|か#|りを仰|<あ#|おげ
Break through myself!
（Break through myself!）
Break through myself!!
（Break through myself!!）
Break through myself!!!
（Break through myself!!!）
Make a stand against
Beat your heart
（Victor…）
（Break through myself）
耳|<み#|みを澄|<すませば
語|<か#|たらずとも聞|<きこえる世|<せ界|<か#|いに
怖|<おじけず踏|<ふみ出|<だせ思|<お#|もうままに
Make a stand against
この音|<お#|とを掲|<か#|かげて
（Break through myself）
（Scream!）
（We are unstoppable）